=Bossy Husband Who Loved Me= =Episode 17=
= الزوج المتسلط الذي أحبني = = الحلقة 17 =
Something's wrong.
هناك خطأ.
In my novel,
في روايتي
Qin Chuan is supposed to be a very unlucky guy.
من المفترض أن يكون تشين تشوان رجلًا سيئ الحظ.
Look at what happened.
انظر إلى ما حدث.
He didn't lose his ledger.
لم يفقد دفتر الأستاذ الخاص به.
They failed to shift the blame on him.
لقد فشلوا في إلقاء اللوم عليه.
He even won the Poetry Contest.
حتى أنه فاز في مسابقة الشعر.
Everything has been going really well for him.
كل شيء يسير على ما يرام بالنسبة له.
And I've become the unlucky one.
وقد أصبحت غير محظوظ.
Did it happen
هل هذا حصل
because I got too close to him?
لأنني اقتربت منه؟
Did he transfer his bad luck to me?
هل نقل سوء حظه إلي؟
I can't let this happen.
لا يمكنني ترك هذا يحدث.
I need to do some calculations.
أحتاج إلى إجراء بعض الحسابات.
He can actually transfer his bad luck to me.
يمكنه في الواقع نقل حظه السيئ إلي.
It seems like
انها تبدو مثل
I need to keep a distance from him from now on.
أحتاج إلى الابتعاد عنه من الآن فصاعدًا.
Let me have a look.
دعني ألقي نظرة.
What is this?
ما هذا؟
The constellation map.
خريطة كوكبة.
What is a constellation map?
ما هي خريطة كوكبة؟
Let me explain it
اسمحوا لي أن أشرح ذلك
in your language.
بلغتك.
This is what you use
هذا ما تستخدمه
to check one's fortune.
للتحقق من ثروة المرء.
So what's the result?
إذن ما هي النتيجة؟
I have extremely bad luck.
لدي حظ سيء للغاية.
It's the Mercury retrograde.
إنه عطارد إلى الوراء.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Since you're married to Prince Rui,
بما أنك متزوجة من الأمير روي ،
you only need to say a word
ما عليك سوى أن تقول كلمة واحدة
and I'll stop anyone from hurting you.
وسأمنع أي شخص من إيذائك.
If you're facing
إذا كنت تواجه
any troubles
أي مشاكل
or difficulties,
أو الصعوبات ،
you can always talk to me.
يمكنك دائما التحدث معي.
Huh?
هاه؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'm a man of my word.
أنا رجل من كلامي.
You don't have to worry about anything.
لا داعي للقلق بشأن أي شيء.
What are you
ما أنت
talking about?
تتحدث عنه؟
I mean...
أعني...
After hearing
بعد الاستماع
my words,
كلماتي،
don't you have anything to say to me?
أليس لديك ما تقوله لي؟
Do you have anything
هل لديك أي شيء
on your mind?
على بالك؟
Yes.
نعم.
I think
أظن
I need to stay away from you.
أحتاج أن أبتعد عنك.
Yes.
نعم.
Stay away from you.
ابتعد عنك.
Further.
إضافي.
The further, the better.
كلما كان ذلك أفضل.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
How did it go?
كيف سار الأمر؟
It seems like I can't read her mind anymore.
يبدو أنني لا أستطيع قراءة رأيها بعد الآن.
From our wedding night
من ليلة زفافنا
to the first time I failed to read her mind,
لأول مرة فشلت في قراءة رأيها ،
it took seven days.
استغرق الأمر سبعة أيام.
I regained the ability when I was at the Mu's Residence.
لقد استعدت القدرة عندما كنت في Mu's Residence.
And it has been seven days since then.
ومرت سبعة أيام منذ ذلك الحين.
It seems like my ability to read her mind
يبدو قدرتي على قراءة رأيها
only lasts
يستمر فقط
for seven days.
لمدة سبعة أيام.
I'm sure
أنا متأكد
Her Highness was extremely moved
صاحبة السمو كان متأثرا للغاية
by Your Highness' words.
بكلمات سموك.
Although she didn't say it out loud,
على الرغم من أنها لم تقل ذلك بصوت عالٍ ،
I'm sure
أنا متأكد
she can't stop thinking about it.
لا يمكنها التوقف عن التفكير في الأمر.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو ،
you need to kiss Her Highness again.
تحتاج إلى تقبيل صاحبة السمو مرة أخرى.
You need to read her mind again,
تحتاج إلى قراءة رأيها مرة أخرى ،
and you'll be able to find out
وستكون قادرًا على معرفة ذلك
who "Yuan Ju Qing" actually is.
من هو "اليوان جو تشينغ" في الواقع.
I sneaked a kiss on her while she was asleep previously,
تسللت إليها قبلة بينما كانت نائمة من قبل ،
and I almost got caught.
وكدت أمسك.
It's not going to be as easy
لن يكون الأمر بهذه السهولة
this time.
هذا الوقت.
I have
أملك
an idea.
فكرة.
Thanks for helping me
شكرا لمساعدتي
when we were at the palace that day.
عندما كنا في القصر في ذلك اليوم.
I've always wanted to thank you.
لطالما أردت أن أشكرك.
Here.
هنا.
Let me propose a toast for you.
دعني أقترح عليك نخبًا.
Why did this guy change his attitude all of a sudden?
لماذا غير هذا الرجل موقفه فجأة؟
He must have an agenda.
يجب أن يكون لديه جدول أعمال.
I need to be careful.
أحتاج أن أكون حذرا.
What Xi did that day
ما فعله شي في ذلك اليوم
was
كنت
very impressive.
مبهر جدا.
Especially the line.
خصوصا الخط.
Just see the over-brimming river
فقط انظر إلى النهر الفائض
flowing east.
تتدفق شرقا.
It's the best line I've ever heard.
إنه أفضل سطر سمعته على الإطلاق.
You wrote
انت كتبت
very good poems
قصائد جيدة جدا
too.
جدا.
They're wonderful.
إنهم رائعون.
How did you manage
كيف نجحتم
to come up with those?
للتوصل إلى هؤلاء؟
It was
كانت
just a coincidence.
مجرد صدفة.
It's not worth mentioning.
لا يستحق الذكر.
(Rubbish.)
(قمامة.)
(You think Li Bai is not worth mentioning, huh?)
(هل تعتقد أن لي باي لا يستحق الذكر ، أليس كذلك؟)
(Why don't you go to hell?)
(لماذا لا تذهب إلى الجحيم؟)
Here.
هنا.
Cheers.
هتافات.
(Why does he keep pouring me drinks?)
(لماذا يسكب لي المشروبات باستمرار؟)
Is he trying to get me drunk
هل يحاول أن يسكر
and get some information out of me?
والحصول على بعض المعلومات مني؟
Xi.
شي.
The wine tastes really good.
النبيذ مذاق جيد حقا.
It's really good.
انه حقا جيد.
Other than poetry,
غير الشعر
Xi gave
أعطى شي
constructible advice
نصيحة قابلة للتنفيذ
to His Majesty as well.
لصاحب الجلالة كذلك.
Your words were thought-provoking.
كانت كلماتك مثيرة للتفكير.
At that time,
فى ذلك التوقيت،
I even thought
حتى أنني فكرت
that we were of the same mind.
أننا كنا من نفس العقل.
Here.
هنا.
Let's drink.
لنشرب.
I...
أنا...
Why do I
لماذا يجب
feel so dizzy?
تشعر بدوار شديد؟
No.
رقم.
I'm a bad drinker.
أنا شارب سيء.
I can't drink anymore.
لا أستطيع أن أشرب بعد الآن.
Xi, you're too humble.
شي ، أنت متواضع جدًا.
You were capable
كنت قادرا
of writing
الكتابة
a great line like,
خط رائع مثل ،
"Our men wouldn't come back till they beat Beiqing."
"رجالنا لن يعودوا حتى يضربوا بيكينغ".
I'm sure you're a good drinker too.
أنا متأكد من أنك شارب جيد أيضًا.
However,
لكن،
I have a question for you.
لدي سؤال لك.
Fire away.
أطلق النار بعيدا.
I wonder
انا اتعجب
if there's a person
إذا كان هناك شخص
you really want to get rid of,
تريد حقًا التخلص منه ،
but also
ولكن أيضا
find it impossible to do so.
تجد أنه من المستحيل القيام بذلك.
Sometimes,
بعض الأحيان،
he even blackmails you.
حتى أنه يبتزك.
Is there a person like that?
هل يوجد شخص مثل هذا؟
Don't worry, Xi.
لا تقلق يا شي.
We're alone here.
نحن وحدنا هنا.
You can tell me everything.
يمكنك إخباري بكل شيء.
Oh.
أوه.
There is.
هنالك.
My
لي
Aunt
عمة
Flo.
فلو.
Her "Aunt Flo"?
"خالتها فلو"؟
Little brat.
طفل شقي.
You won't get anything out of me.
لن تحصل على أي شيء مني.
Do you think you can fool me?
هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع أن تخدعني؟
You're such an amateur.
أنت أحد الهواة.
(Wait.)
(انتظر.)
(Why is he touching my hair?)
(لماذا يلمس شعري؟)
(Why is he still here?)
(لماذا لا يزال هنا؟)
♪I can see heart-shaped bubbles in all seasons♪
♪ أستطيع رؤية فقاعات على شكل قلب في كل الفصول ♪
♪Your beauty is healing me and has become my oxygen♪
جمالك يشفيني وأصبح الأكسجين ♪
♪Without you, it's like the end of the world♪
♪ بدونك ، إنها مثل نهاية العالم
♪The wind stops, leaving behind a trail♪
الريح تتوقف تاركة وراءها أثر ♪
♪I'm hoping that it will rain in my heart♪
♪ آمل أن تمطر في قلبي
♪Trust me. I only want you for the rest of my life♪
♪ صدقني.  أريدك فقط لبقية حياتي ♪
♪I'm obsessed with you, and will travel everywhere for you♪
♪ أنا مهووس بك ، وسأسافر من أجلك في كل مكان
♪Wherever you are, I'll always run to you♪
♪ أينما كنت ، سأركض إليك دائمًا
♪Your smile is magical♪
♪ ابتسامتك ساحرة ♪